verify-email.org 2019-12-31

# Privacy policy

We use cookies to enhance your experience. By continuing to visit this site you agree to our use of cookies. 

* * *

We understand the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of any information you may provide while using the site and our software. Any information we hold about you is provided only by you.

### General Information

In general, we gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what areas of this website are visited most frequently and which of our services are accessed the most. We only use such data in an aggregate form. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you.

### Using Information

We will never sell or share personal information with third parties. We may use this information to serve those users who have requested to be mailed with issues that we feel they may be interested in, such as website and company news. Cookies are used for internal research and to give a better understanding of our audience.

You should also be aware that if you link out to third party websites, they have their own privacy policies for which we can accept no responsibility. Please be certain to check other sites before use.

### Cookies

A cookie is a harmless piece of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard drive. On visiting the website, a cookie will be placed on your computer automatically by the website. We may use two types of cookie from time to time: “persistent cookies” and “session cookies”. Session cookies are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the website and persistent cookies are cookies which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though for how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie). For more information regarding the use of cookies go to http://www.aboutcookies.org. We do not use its persistent or session cookies to store personal information about you.

Third party advertisers may serve cookies via this website but these are only used to serve advertisements from the website's ad servers and to track whether these advertisements are clicked on by visitors to the website. We may pass the non-personal information collected by its cookies to third parties but only for the purposes of carrying out such monitoring, analysis or web log auditing, or for the purposes of tracking the number of anonymous users of the website.

Most browsers accept cookies automatically but you have the ability to accept/decline cookies by altering the settings in your browser. If you decline/disable cookies, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of the website or the website may not be available to you.

### Security

The website is protected against unauthorised access using the latest security devices and firewalls.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to add to or change the terms of this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion, without prior notice to you. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on the website, and it will become effective from the time of posting to the website. Please visit this Privacy Policy on a regular basis to make sure you have read the latest version and you understand what we do with your information.

### GDPR Compliance

The website is in Compliance with the EU GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) made affective on 25th May 2018\. Please refer to <https://verify-email.org/gdpr.html>

All data, including email addresses verified via our website or services, is not disclosed to any third-parties as persons or organizations. We handle your information responsibly and with respect. All customers’ data is protected and kept safe.
